<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Spring trees and evening clouds</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/</link>
        <description>Recent content on Spring trees and evening clouds</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>春树暮云</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://brume.top/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Reading</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/reading/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://brume.top/en/reading/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Due to the differences in the titles of books published in different countries, accuracy cannot be guaranteed when translating, I apologize that this page is only available in Chinese.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Glance back to Changsha: like cicadas shed their shell, soaring above the dust.</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/p/a-trip-to-changsha/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://brume.top/en/p/a-trip-to-changsha/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://dongli.pages.dev/file/1f6893647f31558236123.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Glance back to Changsha: like cicadas shed their shell, soaring above the dust." /&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By the shore, I wash my feet,&lt;br&gt;
As night’s shadows with currents meet.&lt;br&gt;
In morning light, my short hair dries,&lt;br&gt;
With gentle breezes whispering sighs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Through Wu’s mountains and Chu’s lakes I roam,&lt;br&gt;
Yet long for Xiang, my heart’s true home.&lt;br&gt;
I buy a boat, my cares I leave,&lt;br&gt;
Returning from office, free to believe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Heaven’s favor guides my way,&lt;br&gt;
In June’s warm embrace, I’ll drift and sway,&lt;br&gt;
With fair winds lifting me on the tide,&lt;br&gt;
Floating through waves, I take my stride.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Lofty thoughts, like cicadas shed their shell,&lt;br&gt;
Soaring above the dust.&lt;br&gt;
Like Zhuangzi dreaming of butterfly flight,&lt;br&gt;
I wander where waters and clouds unite.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Faintly I envision—garments of lotus green,&lt;br&gt;
Adorned with autumn orchids, a grace serene,&lt;br&gt;
Attired in elegance, shedding earthly bind.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The goddess of Xiang with a charming smile,&lt;br&gt;
Dances in robes, graceful all the while.&lt;br&gt;
Her delicate fingers pluck strings with care,&lt;br&gt;
Releasing a haunting tune into the air.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Awakening Qu Yuan’s loyal pain,&lt;br&gt;
In &amp;ldquo;Nine Songs&amp;rdquo;, his vows remain.&lt;br&gt;
Words that shine, like sun and moon,&lt;br&gt;
Flow from his sleeve, a timeless tune.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Oh, let not the children know this delight,&lt;br&gt;
The river’s dreams are ours to write.&lt;br&gt;
For this joy in rowing, vast and grand,&lt;br&gt;
Is a treasure meant for our own hand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The upper poem is the translated version of a poem from the Song Dynasty by Zhang Xiaoxiang.It is the work of Zhang Xiaoxiang when he was boating on the Xiangjiang River on the way back to the north. The original poem is shown below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;濯足夜滩急，晞发北风凉。吴山楚泽行遍，只欠到潇湘。买得扁舟归去，此事天公付我，六月下沧浪。蝉蜕尘埃外，蝶梦水云乡。&lt;br&gt;制荷衣，纫兰佩，把琼芳。湘妃起舞一笑，抚瑟奏清商。唤起九歌忠愤，拂拭三闾文字，还与日争光。莫遣儿辈觉，此乐未渠央。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, our school organized a study trip to Hunan, spanning five days. During this time, we traveled between Changsha and Shaoshan, exploring both rural and urban landscapes, witnessing the fusion and collision of traditional culture and modern society, strolling by the lakes and rivers, and contemplating the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;day-1-setting-off&#34;&gt;Day 1: Setting Off!
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Midday, the entire grade, teachers, and staff gathered at Shenzhen North Railway Station, to board the high-speed train bound for Changsha. Arriving at noon, the weather was surprisingly mild, a rare treat in the South.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/df5adcca9f980df039859.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;深圳北站远景&#34;
	
	
&gt;
△A faraway look of Shenzhen North Railway Station&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After an hour’s wait, we finally boarded the sleek Fuxing Electric Multiple Unit. Its modern design and technology showcased our school’s commitment to student comfort and efficiency. Riding the high-speed rail instead of the slower options not only enhanced our travel experience, but also reflected our nation’s advancements in transportation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/e41e2239142abfb175247.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;高铁车头&#34;
	
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/618e199679baf4e3e05c6.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;复兴号&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before boarding, I snapped a few photos of the train as I walked along.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scenery outside the window, from the alluvial plains of the Pearl River Delta to the karst landscapes of northern Guangdong, and the hills and plains of both southern and northern Hunan, was all breathtaking!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approaching Guangzhou, rain began to fall, adding a touch of Jiangnan charm to our journey as we glimpsed barges on distant rivers under misty skies.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/25d27fa4a35b5c16896d5.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;一条河，应该是珠江的支流&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then we made stops at Shaoguan, Chenzhou, and Hengyang before arriving at Changsha South Station, a journey of approximately three and a half hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/090ef6ec71df637ea0906.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;长沙南站附近的公路&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From there, we boarded a bus near Changsha South Station. I was fortunate to sit in the front row, offering one of the best views. After a meal and a nighttime cruise on the Liuyang River, we stayed overnight at a hotel near Huanghua Airport, concluding our first day’s journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;day-2-blending-old-with-new&#34;&gt;Day 2: Blending Old with New
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Returning to downtown Changsha, we began the day with a visit to the Hunan Provincial Museum, renowned for its artifacts excavated from the Han Dynasty tombs at Mawangdui. On the third floor, we watched a captivating light show played every half hour on the tomb’s sidewalls. Shadows danced on walls over ten meters deep, bringing to life ancient clothing and auspicious patterns, evoking a sense of reverence and mystery akin to a religious experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/650e1f5638bdcd4491cd8.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;灯光演出，看台上挤满了人&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The picture below is a picture of the grave pit before the performance. You can refer to the people in the stands and estimate the depth of the triangle with the relevant knowledge of the triangle that you learned in junior high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/c2b72f84962b60c214622.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;墓坑&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, we crossed the Xiang River to visit Hunan University, Yuelu Academy, and Aiwan Pavilion. Known as a &amp;ldquo;millennium-old academy,&amp;rdquo; Hunan University exudes a strong academic atmosphere amidst serene surroundings. At the entrance, university students dressed in traditional attire added youthful vigor to the campus.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/dcb3f561ce97af139d5c7.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;湖南大学的一栋建筑&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, we explored Yuelu Academy. Towering ancient trees and flowing waters adorned the site, where every stone inscription and historic building reflected the deep cultural heritage of Hunan. Amidst these ancient halls, we connected with the wisdom of past scholars, experiencing firsthand the cultural richness encapsulated in the phrase, &amp;ldquo;Only Chu produces talent, and here it reaches its peak(惟楚有材，于斯为盛)&amp;rdquo;.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/dab50c233fc26466d37d7.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;惟楚有材，于斯为盛&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continuing north from the academy towards Aiwan Pavilion, we encountered Tang Bohu’s poetic sentiment. Despite it is now the modern era, it was difficult not to imagine Tang Bohu’s leisurely mood at that time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I paint the azure Yangtze’s flow,&lt;br&gt;Maple leaves at Aiwan Pavilion woe.&lt;br&gt;Autumn moon gently bathes the Buddhist shrine,&lt;br&gt;Incense smoke curls around the scripture hall divine.&lt;br&gt;(我画蓝江水悠悠，爱晚亭上枫叶愁。秋月溶溶照佛寺，香烟袅袅绕经楼。)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/499cea4a396e002b78089.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;爱晚亭&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We then returned along the same route to visit Taiping Old Street for field research (actually, it was shopping). Despite being touted as &amp;ldquo;the street with the most intact original street pattern of ancient Changsha,&amp;rdquo; it unfortunately fell short of preserving its cultural essence, appearing somewhat homogeneous and commercialized. Adjacent sites, such as Jia Yi’s former residence, seemed out of place.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/dc6b915c65fc9d3cf50ab.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;太平老街&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, Taiping Old Street’s &amp;ldquo;Black Classic&amp;rdquo; stinky tofu was indeed delicious and reasonably priced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During free time on Taiping Old Street, I experienced Changsha’s metro system. The stations resembled those in Shenzhen, but amenities inside the Shenzhen metro trains, such as display screens, announcements, and station cleanliness, surpassed those in Changsha’s metro.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/739ad4a3931b28f7658d3.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;长沙地铁&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;day-3-embracing-tradition&#34;&gt;Day 3: Embracing Tradition
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;From Changsha to Shaoshan, our journey took about three hours, arriving at the research and practice base in Huangtian Village, where we met local farmers and engaged in activities such as fishing in rice fields and transplanting seedlings, followed by a meal at a farmhouse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huangtian Village’s picturesque surroundings included roadside encounters with some unnamed wildflowers.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/2f0463b6f5d91446dd0da.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;黄田村野花&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, we visited the Mao Zedong Memorial Museum in Shaoshan, learning about Chairman Mao’s leadership in completing China’s historical tasks against imperialism and feudalism, establishing the People’s Republic of China, and advancing socialism’s glorious history. Afterwards, we visited the great man’s former residence. The environment was excellent, with a half-acre lotus pond in front of the house, giving it a feeling of &amp;ldquo;repeating lakes and overlapping peaks, clear and splendid&amp;rdquo;.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/30b5d6cc284310b6dfd78.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;毛主席故居&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nearby, I unexpectedly met two middle school classmates who were also participating in the study tour, now attending another high school. We discussed our studies and lives over the past year and the new changes in our lives as we entered a new stage. Finally, we took a group photo and parted ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After dinner, we watched the large-scale live performance &amp;ldquo;China Gave Birth to Mao Zedong&amp;rdquo; in Shaoshan. We watched from a high platform, enjoying the spacious venue. Opening my map app on my phone, I surprisingly found a satellite image that clearly resembled a map of China. (Taiwan Province and Hainan Province are on the bottom right of the theater.)
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/03170402df8a6ce2a87ff-c0a7d1b2bffe126517.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;satellite image&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scene at the event was as shown in the following image. The dazzling lights of the performance were truly awe-inspiring.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/ea560c7437020a4044373.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;演出&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We stayed overnight at a hotel in the Huitang town near Changsha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;day-4-inspiring-our-nation&#34;&gt;Day 4: Inspiring Our Nation
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Returning to Changsha after more than two hours by bus, we visited the First Normal School in the morning, Chairman Mao’s alma mater. In the afternoon, we visited Orange Island.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Orange Island sits atop the Xiang River, with a narrow and elongated shape. We took a small train from the north of Orange Island, heading south to the tip of Orange Island. The school planned for the entire grade to take a large group photo on the square at the tip of Orange Island. We arrived early and had spare time to stroll along the shore with classmates. The slow flow of the Xiang River and its wide surface offered a pleasant view of the water flowing south and many boats passing by.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/4f0650ecaaac5f79a4124.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;湘江&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Song Dynasty poet Zhang Xiaoxiang praised:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;濯足夜滩急，晞发北风凉。吴山楚泽行遍，只欠到潇湘。买得扁舟归去，此事天公付我，六月下沧浪。蝉蜕尘埃外，蝶梦水云乡。&lt;br&gt;制荷衣，纫兰佩，把琼芳。湘妃起舞一笑，抚瑟奏清商。唤起九歌忠愤，拂拭三闾文字，还与日争光。莫遣儿辈觉，此乐未渠央。(English translation is shown on the top of the page)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really like the meaning in this lyric, a blend of Su Shi’s broad-mindedness and Li Qingzhao’s fresh and elegant style, between a clear and high-minded mood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After taking the group photo, we went to the Mao Zedong Youth Art Statue north of Orange Isle. The sculpture’s eyes were bright, just like Chairman Mao’s &amp;ldquo;We criticized with all our might, pointing to stream and hill, writing in blame or praise (指点江山，激扬文字)&amp;rdquo; demeanor.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/126a152ca347a34270d31.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;雕像&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later in the evening, we returned near Shaoshan and held a bonfire party. The fireworks at the bonfire party were exciting, breaking the silence of the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align =&#34;center&#34;&gt;&lt;video src=&#34;https://video.gumlet.io/65b99c6ae5f634aafa2ef6a0/668a43c4517fbad3e8038e27/download.mp4&#34; controls=&#34;controls&#34; width=&#34;80%&#34; &gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I can’t sing, I didn’t sign up for the class chorus performance. However, during our class performance, a few of my good friends lifted me onto the stage. This scene was seen by my classmates who work at the TV station, who filmed it as a &amp;ldquo;highlight&amp;rdquo; of the event and aired it on the TV program. Now I’m somewhat famous throughout the school~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;day-5returning-home&#34;&gt;Day 5：Returning Home
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the morning, we visited the Yuan Longping Rice Museum, and in the afternoon, we took the high-speed train back to Shenzhen by evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/fc26ba5b1b84c626256d4.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;速度&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the return train made fewer stops, we arrived at the Shenzhen North Railway Station in three hours. We dispersed near it, concluding our study tour successfully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this study tour, we learned about culture, history, and heritage. Today, in the midst of prosperity and standing in the grand tide of the &amp;ldquo;great changes unseen in a century&amp;rdquo;, we are fortunate to have an unprecedented broad vision, to stand at the pinnacle of history, and to look forward to the distant and brilliant future. The magnificent picture of national rejuvenation slowly unfolds before our eyes, inspiring and urging us forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Therefore, as the gatherers of new knowledge, explorers of new thoughts, and the surfers of the new era, we naturally shoulder a heavy and sacred mission. &amp;ldquo;So many deeds cry out to be done, and always urgently; the world rolls on, time presses. (多少事，从来急，天地转，光阴迫)&amp;rdquo; As the future of the nation and the hope of the nation, we deeply understand the weight of responsibility and the honor of the mission. We pledge to use China’s unique wisdom, innovative solutions, and firm actions to outline and shape a better world tomorrow, allowing China’s voice to resonate globally and making the world more splendid because of our young generation!
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/1515c655213246bca8129.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;#&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Long dreams</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/p/long-dreams/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://brume.top/en/p/long-dreams/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://dongli.pages.dev/file/74beaf2497a1c52909704.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Long dreams" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blog has been running smoothly for a year now, and the thought fills me with excitement! Reaching this one-year milestone, I look back at the journey with a flood of emotions and thoughts rushing in like waves. It&amp;rsquo;s a moment filled with reflection, and I pen this to mark the occasion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been planning this article for a while, and as I drafted it, the title &amp;ldquo;The Long Dream&amp;rdquo; repeatedly came to mind. Life, after all, feels like a dream. I believe it symbolizes my reflections on life and my philosophical quest, while also mirroring the long journey that countless people embark on in pursuit of truth and the meaning of existence.
&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://brume.top/p/hello-world/&#34; &gt;&lt;em&gt;Hello World&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Spring Trees, Evening Clouds&amp;rdquo; is more than just a blog, it&amp;rsquo;s a sanctuary for my soul. Since the end of 2022, I&amp;rsquo;ve been sharing my explorations and discoveries here with my readers. Through my writing, it&amp;rsquo;s clear that life is like an extended dream. Whether in high school, university, or stepping into society later on, we all build dreams and chase them at different stages. Pausing from time to time allows us to rethink, recalibrate, and help the humble me refocus on future explorations.
&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://brume.top/p/long-dreams/&#34; &gt;&lt;em&gt;Long dreams&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking back, I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced both glory and humiliation, seems sometimes basked in spring breezes and sometimes weathered frost and snow. I understand now that life is a long and intricate journey. This is precisely why I hold myself to higher standards, to courageously follow my dreams and fearlessly break free from my cocoon. Don&amp;rsquo;t let uncertainty scare you, because it is uncertainty that awakens our deepest potential.
&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://brume.top/p/certainty-and-uncertainty/&#34; &gt;&lt;em&gt;Certainty and Uncertainty&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we clear away the fog of life, we&amp;rsquo;ll encounter countless questions and challenges. We will stumble and fall, get hurt, but we will also rise again. This, I believe, is the true essence of life—a great and authentic life requires facing trials and turbulence, for only through such struggles can miracles unfold. I imagine that even us smallest human beings, through writing, can create something grand and magnificent in our lives.
&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://brume.top/p/restart/&#34; &gt;&lt;em&gt;Restart&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one-year anniversary marks only a new beginning for the blog, but my exploration and reflection are far from over. I will continue to face new challenges, embrace new opportunities, and gather new knowledge and experiences. I hope that after some time, I&amp;rsquo;ll return here with richer insights to share with you all once again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, I want to thank every reader of this blog. Your support and encouragement fuel my drive to move forward. Please remember, even though the blog updates may be sporadic, the exploration and reflection of the soul never cease. Let&amp;rsquo;s continue to follow this &amp;ldquo;Long Dream,&amp;rdquo; delving into the deeper philosophies of life. &amp;ldquo;Raise your glass to the east wind, and let&amp;rsquo;s face the future together with ease!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align=&#34;right&#34;&gt;Greetings from the bottom of my heart&lt;br&gt;Zephyr Easton&lt;br&gt;Dec. 31, 2023&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/74beaf2497a1c52909704.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;nature.jpg&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Web 2 Pwa</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/p/web-2-pwa/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://brume.top/en/p/web-2-pwa/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://dongli.pages.dev/file/182760af93f035e9f2c31.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Web 2 Pwa" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is after today&amp;rsquo;s exam, I summarize my experience and tutorial of making the site adapt to PWA.&lt;del&gt;boring&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-pwa&#34;&gt;What is PWA
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;PWA (Progressive Web App) is a technology and method used to develop web applications. PWA combine the best features of traditional web apps and native mobile apps to provide a better user experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PWA can be accessed through a browser and do not need to be installed on the device, but they have similar functionality and features to native apps. PWA make use of APIs provided by web browsers, such as &lt;strong&gt;Service Workers&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Web App Manifest&lt;/strong&gt;, to enable applications to work offline, push notifications, and add to the home screen. These features allow PWA to run in a consistent way across platforms and devices, without the need to download and install them from the app store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://web.dev/progressive-web-apps/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Learn more about PWA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;check-if-your-browser-supports-pwa&#34;&gt;Check if your browser supports PWA
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recommend checking on caniuse.com to see if a browser supports PWA
&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://caniuse.com/?search=pwa&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you open the website, the page looks like this ▽
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/4604d338361e9217ebd49.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;caniuse.com 上的截图&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;build-a-pwa&#34;&gt;Build a PWA
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, build a PWA to a website can be done in the following steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full-site HTTPS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code &lt;code&gt;manifest.json&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;sw.js&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare app icons for 192×192px and 512×512px&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring in &lt;code&gt;manifest.json&lt;/code&gt; files and &lt;code&gt;sw.js&lt;/code&gt; files on relevant pages of your website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next is my own practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;manifestjson&#34;&gt;manifest.json
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;lntable&#34;&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 1
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 2
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 3
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 4
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 5
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 6
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 7
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 8
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 9
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;10
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;11
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;12
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;13
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;14
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;15
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;16
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;17
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;18
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;19
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;20
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-json&#34; data-lang=&#34;json&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;name&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;春树暮云&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// the name that start screen displays
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;short_name&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;春树暮云&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// the name of the PWA
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;theme_color&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;#f6ffff&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// theme color
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;background_color&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;#f6ffff&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// background color
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;display&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;fullscreen&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// starting transition animation, standalone or fullscreen
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;scope&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;/&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;start_url&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;/&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// start page&amp;#39;s URL
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;icons&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;        &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;            &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;src&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;192.png&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// Rewrite according to the path of your icon
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;            &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;sizes&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;192x192&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;            &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;type&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;image/png&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;        &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;},&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;        &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;            &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;src&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;512.png&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;            &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;sizes&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;512x512&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;            &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;type&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;image/png&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;        &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;],&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The above code can be changed according to the actual situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;swjs&#34;&gt;sw.js
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;lntable&#34;&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 1
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 2
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 3
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 4
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 5
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 6
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 7
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 8
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 9
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;10
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;11
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;12
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;13
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;14
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;15
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;16
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;17
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;18
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;19
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;20
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;21
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;22
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;23
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;24
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;25
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;26
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;27
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;28
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;29
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;30
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;31
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;32
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;33
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;34
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;35
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;36
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;37
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;38
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;39
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;40
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;41
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;42
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;43
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;44
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;45
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;46
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;47
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;48
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;49
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;50
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;51
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;52
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;53
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;54
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-javascript&#34; data-lang=&#34;javascript&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;use strict&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// Declare that the entire script is in strict mode
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;kr&#34;&gt;const&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;cacheName&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;PWA-cache&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// the name of the cache
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;kr&#34;&gt;const&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;startPage&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;https://example.com&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;kr&#34;&gt;const&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;offlinePage&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;https://example.com&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;kr&#34;&gt;const&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;filesToCache&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;startPage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;offlinePage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;];&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;kr&#34;&gt;const&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;neverCacheUrls&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;sr&#34;&gt;/admin/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;];&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// Never cache directories, such as the &amp;#34;Admin&amp;#34; folder in Typecho
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;self&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;addEventListener&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;install&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;kd&#34;&gt;function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;console&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;log&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;Cache event!&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;waitUntil&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// When installing, cache the files that need to be cached
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;caches&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;open&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;cacheStorageKey&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;then&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;kd&#34;&gt;function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;cache&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;console&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;log&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;Adding to Cache:&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;cacheList&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;cache&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;addAll&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;cacheList&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;}).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;then&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;kd&#34;&gt;function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;()&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;console&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;log&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;Skip waiting!&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;self&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;skipWaiting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;()&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;})&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;})&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;self&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;addEventListener&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;activate&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;kd&#34;&gt;function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// Determine whether the address needs to be requested in real time, and if so, continue to send the request
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;console&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;log&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;Activate event&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;waitUntil&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;nb&#34;&gt;Promise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;all&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;caches&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;keys&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;().&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;then&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;cacheNames&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;        &lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;cacheNames&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;map&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;          &lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;if&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;!==&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;cacheStorageKey&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;            &lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;caches&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;delete&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;          &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;        &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;})&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;})&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;then&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(()&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;console&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;log&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;Clients claims.&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;self&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;clients&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;claim&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;()&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;})&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;})&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;self&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;addEventListener&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;fetch&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;kd&#34;&gt;function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// When a cache resource is matched, the data is returned from the cache
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;respondWith&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;caches&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;request&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;then&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;kd&#34;&gt;function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;response&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;if&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;response&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;!=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;kc&#34;&gt;null&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;        &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;console&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;log&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;Using cache for:&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;request&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;        &lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;response&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;console&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;log&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;Fallback to fetch:&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;request&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;fetch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;request&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;})&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;})&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;ingest-files&#34;&gt;Ingest files
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ingest &lt;code&gt;manifest.json&lt;/code&gt; in the &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;head&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; tag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;lntable&#34;&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;1
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-HTML&#34; data-lang=&#34;HTML&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;link&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;rel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;manifest&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;href&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;manifest.json&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;crossorigin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;anonymous&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;/&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, check whether the &lt;em&gt;serviceWorker&lt;/em&gt; is registered in the tag &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;body&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;lntable&#34;&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 1
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 2
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 3
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 4
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 5
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 6
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 7
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 8
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 9
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;10
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-HTML&#34; data-lang=&#34;HTML&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;script&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;type&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;text/javascript&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;if&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;navigator&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;serviceWorker&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;!=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;kc&#34;&gt;null&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;        &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;navigator&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;serviceWorker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;register&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;sw.js&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;            &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;then&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;kd&#34;&gt;function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;registration&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;                &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;console&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;log&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;Registered events at scope: &amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;registration&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;scope&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;            &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;}).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;catch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;kd&#34;&gt;function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;err&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;                &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;console&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;log&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;Registered events at fail: &amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;err&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;            &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;});&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;script&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this point, the PWA has been adapted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, in blogging systems such as TypeCho or WordPress, it is easy to have unsuccessful adaptation due to various reasons. At this point, you can optionally guide the user to manually configure the PWA, for example, by clicking a button.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s the code:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;lntable&#34;&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 1
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 2
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 3
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 4
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 5
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 6
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 7
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 8
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt; 9
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;10
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;11
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;12
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;13
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;14
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;15
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;16
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;17
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;18
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;19
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;20
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;21
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;22
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;23
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;24
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-HTML&#34; data-lang=&#34;HTML&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;script&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  	&lt;span class=&#34;kd&#34;&gt;var&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;deferredPrompt&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;kc&#34;&gt;null&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;		&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// 判断用户是否安装此应用：beforeinstallprompt,如果用户已经安装过了,那么该事件不会再次触发
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  	&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// 需要卸载，然后重新打开浏览器才能再次触发
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;nb&#34;&gt;window&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;addEventListener&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;beforeinstallprompt&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;e&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;preventDefault&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;();&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;deferredPrompt&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;});&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  	&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// 安装完成后触发,即点击安装弹窗中的“安装”后被触发
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;nb&#34;&gt;window&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;addEventListener&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;appinstalled&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;()&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;deferredPrompt&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;kc&#34;&gt;null&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;});&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;kd&#34;&gt;function&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;addToDesktop&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;()&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;// 调用prompt()方法触发安装弹窗
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c1&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;deferredPrompt&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;prompt&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;();&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;      &lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;deferredPrompt&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;kc&#34;&gt;null&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;script&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt; 
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;button&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;onclick&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;addToDesktop()&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;点击安装PWA&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;button&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The demonstration is as follows:
&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;#&#34; &gt;Due to the replacement of the blog system, this link has failed, and I will try to configure PWA for this site when I have time in the future&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, to avoid compatibility issues, it is recommended that you place the &lt;code&gt;manifest.json&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;sw.js&lt;/code&gt; files in the root directory of your website when deploying your PWA.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Certainty and Uncertainty</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/p/certainty-and-uncertainty/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://brume.top/en/p/certainty-and-uncertainty/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://e7a23aee.dongli.pages.dev/file/2318bc833d140a44d2df0.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Certainty and Uncertainty" /&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mighty desert is burning for the love of a blade of grass who shakes her head and laughs and flies away.&lt;br&gt;&lt;p align=&#34;right&#34;&gt;&lt;i&gt;Stray Birds&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This afternoon, I was heading home from school. The return trip was packed, and I was sitting side by side with a classmate. When he reached his stop, I leaned aside to let him pass. As he was leaving, he asked me, &amp;ldquo;Are you the student who gave a speech on stage before?&amp;rdquo; I nodded. Due to the success of my previous speech on philosophy, many freshmen knew me, but I couldn’t recall their names. This wasn’t the first time I encountered this situation. After getting off the bus, I walked with a friend, pondering a question in my mind: how did my speeches begin and why were they successful?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In middle school, my first formal speech was in May 2022. The success of that speech had an element of chance, but it laid the foundation for my subsequent speeches. Coinciding with the 100th anniversary of the Communist Youth League, my homeroom teacher selected me as the speaker for the flag-raising ceremony. After discussing with teachers, I chose &amp;ldquo;Chasing Dreams in Youth, Striving in the Era&amp;rdquo; as the theme. This speech under the national flag received a warm response.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In August of the same year, the grade recommended me to speak at the opening ceremony, encouraging classmates to strive for their youth goals. A few days before the school year started, I came to school to prepare and coincidentally met the new grade director. She had heard my previous speech, had confidence in my abilities, and offered some suggestions for improvement for this speech. However, due to the pandemic, the school opening was delayed, and the speech was put on hold. It wasn’t until December 2022, after mid-term exams, that our grade held an online congress. At noon that day, I participated in a video recording in the school’s party member activity room with other relevant students. In the afternoon, my speech shook the grade, with applause and cheers from other classes and gave me a lot of encouragement. Perhaps it was these successes of my speech that led more kindred friends to recognize my abilities and recommend me to continue speaking in this new collective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The third speech was more low-profile and took place when the new class was created in February of this year. The class teacher and some students thought that the opening of the class should have a ceremony, so I was nominated to speak with the class president.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fourth speech was the one mentioned at the beginning of this article.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking back, although my first speech was accidental, it paved the way for a series of speeches afterwards. Many friends think that with my continuous efforts, chance gradually turns into certainty. This also means that when selecting speakers, uncertainty is gradually becoming uniform (Of course, this is just one’s view, and I think that many of my high school classmates are much more competent than me, and they may become the next ones to be nominated. I am clearly aware of this).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes I complain to my friends that I have to make three public speeches in the last month, which is too tiring; but sometimes I feel very lucky to be trusted and recognized by teachers and friends. A completely certain world is boring; a world full of uncertainty is impermanent and terrifying. I want to ask myself: how do we mediate?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://e7a23aee.dongli.pages.dev/file/2318bc833d140a44d2df0.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;世界是不能一言以蔽的，她是复杂的&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Try to think deeply about these two concepts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Uncertainty gives us the opportunity to innovate and progress. We live in a world that is always unknown. When the future is filled with unknowns, we no longer rely on past experiences and established patterns. Instead of sticking to traditions, we need to look for new methods, new strategies, and new opportunities. It is in moments of uncertainty that we challenge ourselves, surpass our limits, and embrace new possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From my perspective, both certainty and uncertainty provide opportunities for personal growth and development. As mentioned earlier regarding my speeches—in a certain environment, although our inertia can be daunting and we might fall into a comfort zone, lacking motivation for new experiences and challenges… But it is during moments of uncertainty and transformation that we can adapt to new environments and situations more swiftly, much like when we leave our former collective and arrive at a new high school! I dare to predict that this adaptability will indeed make us more independent and resilient, surely helping to enhance our skills in various aspects of our lives!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moreover, by learning from uncertainty and accumulating experiences, we can cultivate better problem-solving abilities. These opportunities for growth can make us more competitive and prepare us for a future that aligns with the ideals of &amp;ldquo;comprehensive development&amp;rdquo; advocated by our Party, nation, and society.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the long run, whether it is certainty or uncertainty, the influence and transformation it brings to an individual is an &lt;strong&gt;utterly misleading proposition&lt;/strong&gt;! Every person is a &amp;ldquo;node&amp;rdquo; in the vast web of society, and personal growth is inseparable from social contexts! My ability to be recognized for my speeches isn’t due to certainty; rather, it stems from the effort I’ve put into this endeavor. Extending this thought further, the achievements of our school are not solely determined by &amp;ldquo;certainty&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;uncertainty&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ni Dieu, ni César, ni tribun &lt;br&gt;Producteurs, sauvons-nous nous-mêmes!&lt;p align=&#34;right&#34;&gt;L’Internationale&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both certainty and uncertainty can only play a facilitating role in personal growth; the ultimate decision-making power lies within our own hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I write this, I feel that many of my friends around me are, to varying degrees, infatuated with the notions of “certainty” and “uncertainty.” I recall a classmate from another Province earlier this year, who upon hearing inappropriate remarks from a lecturer during a talk, seized the microphone and resolutely proclaimed, &amp;ldquo;We study for the great rejuvenation of the Chinese nation!&amp;rdquo; I admire this classmate’s grand vision and expansive perspective. We are the youth of a new era in China. It is our significant responsibility to ensure that we, as young people, have poetry and the distant future in our eyes! Studying is not merely about learning a few English words or mathematical symbols; more importantly, it is about cultivating a broad mind and a wide vision! This has nothing to do with one’s gentle or rough character, nor with &amp;ldquo;certainty&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;uncertainty&amp;rdquo;! Among the great figures in modern Chinese history—leaders like Chairman Mao, Qu Qiubai, Chen Duxiu, and General Peng, each had distinct personalities, yet they are all remarkable figures in the glorious history of our nation. &amp;ldquo;In books, there are beautiful faces; in books, there are houses of gold.&amp;rdquo; As one of the top 5% students in Shenzhen(Said by our teachers), how can we have a narrow vision, or even shy away from putting our ideas on the table? Young people should understand from an early age: &amp;ldquo;Read thousands of classic texts and walk a thousand miles of life’s journey!&amp;rdquo; Be resolute in adversity and never lose sight of lofty ambitions! Strive for higher goals, seek broader horizons, and maintain a grounded demeanor! Those who are near excellent people would turn excellent; those who are near bad guys may turn bad! Studying is not about seeking a so called &amp;ldquo;certainty&amp;rdquo; for survival but about cultivating oneself, managing one’s family, governing the nation, and bringing peace to the world! Studying is also about establishing one’s own heart, setting examples for friends, bringing honor to one’s family, working for one’s country, and possessing the ability to foster peace for all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/29147782810f1e76c89aa.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;横渠四句&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this world filled with opportunities and challenges, seizing opportunities is crucial for both individuals and society. How do we gracefully face certainty and uncertainty? How do we seize opportunities and respond to challenges? These are fundamental questions that each of us needs to contemplate.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Huge Revolution that AI has Brought in the Field of QR Codes</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/p/the-huge-revolution-that-ai-has-brought-in-the-field-of-qr-code/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://brume.top/en/p/the-huge-revolution-that-ai-has-brought-in-the-field-of-qr-code/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://dongli.pages.dev/file/366fe8fab8b6919f01237.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The Huge Revolution that AI has Brought in the Field of QR Codes" /&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In recent years, the rapid development of AI technology has profoundly changed our way of life. QR codes, as a fast and convenient tool for information transmission, have also been widely used globally. This article aims to explore the transformation brought by AI in the field of &lt;strong&gt;QR codes&lt;/strong&gt; and to elaborate on its positive impact on people&amp;rsquo;s lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;enhancing-the-speed-and-accuracy-of-qr-code-recognition&#34;&gt;Enhancing the Speed and Accuracy of QR Code Recognition
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;By utilizing deep learning, image processing, and other technologies, AI can quickly identify QR codes from complex backgrounds and correct issues such as tilt, blurriness, and obstruction, thereby improving recognition efficiency and user experience. (This means that some &amp;ldquo;fancy&amp;rdquo; QR codes are about to reach their potential.) For example, take a look at the image below:
&lt;img src=&#34;https://e7a23aee.dongli.pages.dev/file/be81054b13c41284f5934.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;一张倾斜放置的二维码&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;expanding-application-areas&#34;&gt;Expanding Application Areas
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The introduction of AI technology has brought enormous expansion opportunities to the application areas of QR codes. With AI algorithms, QR codes can be seamlessly integrated with images, becoming more aesthetically pleasing and possessing greater developmental potential. Platforms like &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://qrbtf.com/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;qrbtf&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://quickqr.art/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;quickqr&lt;/a&gt; have ventured into the AI field, creating QR codes that evoke a sense of peering into reality from cyberspace. I believe this will spark a significant transformation across many industries. These new QR codes create a fantastical and extraordinary interface, far surpassing the chaotic reality represented by traditional QR codes. For example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://e7a23aee.dongli.pages.dev/file/ea83a257cd8cb6033c5d5.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;美轮美奂的境界&#34;
	
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://e7a23aee.dongli.pages.dev/file/deaac71386d1fc9d66650.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;巧妙的融合&#34;
	
	
&gt;
(The first image was created by a research team in China, showcasing a scene of dusk and dawn amidst the white mountains and black waters, with poetic beauty. The second image was created by a foreign research team, cleverly integrating a cat made of building blocks into the image, presenting a unique aesthetic. I must admit that this is a masterpiece of AI.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;promoting-business-innovation&#34;&gt;Promoting Business Innovation
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This topic has also been a point of discussion with friends, and this article only explores its positive impacts. The widespread application of AI technology in the field of QR codes has had a positive effect on business innovation. From the previous two images, it’s evident that the intelligent application of QR codes provides new opportunities and business models.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(If you need to validate my hypothesis, experiments can be conducted to analyze the data from scanned QR codes, helping relevant parties understand consumer preferences and execute precise marketing and promotions.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In my view, the innovation of QR codes has sparked the potential for business development, providing companies with a greater competitive advantage.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-impact-of-new-qr-codes-on-the-cultural-industry&#34;&gt;The Impact of New QR Codes on the Cultural Industry
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In my opinion, new QR codes will bring &amp;ldquo;disruptive&amp;rdquo; changes to the cultural industry. Integrating traditional Chinese culture into QR codes will help promote the creative transformation and innovative development of outstanding traditional Chinese culture. Furthermore, AI-generated QR codes can also combine with two-dimensional culture to drive new developments. For example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://e7a23aee.dongli.pages.dev/file/c7c184b0d59981ccf87e2.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;qrbtf官方制作的动漫风格的二维码&#34;
	
	
&gt;
△Anime-style QR code created by qrbtf&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://e7a23aee.dongli.pages.dev/file/341e570e45c831d315da0.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;qrbtf官方制作的油画风格的二维码&#34;
	
	
&gt;
△Oil painting-style QR code created by qrbtf&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://e7a23aee.dongli.pages.dev/file/edcdab10048ebc72413cd.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;qrbtf官方制作的青花瓷风格的二维码&#34;
	
	
&gt;
△Blue and white porcelain-style QR code created by qrbtf&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-mechanism-behind-ai-generated-qr-codes&#34;&gt;The Mechanism Behind AI-Generated QR Codes
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use relevant software to generate a QR code image.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beautify the image using Stable Diffusion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although it seems straightforward, the actual operation can be a bit cumbersome. Typically, Stable Diffusion has high requirements for device configuration. Consequently, relevant developers have created web versions of Stable Diffusion (using shared GPUs with limited functions), such as DreamStudio and Stable Diffusion on Hugging Face Spaces, as well as the qrbtf website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;practical-examples&#34;&gt;Practical Examples
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://e7a23aee.dongli.pages.dev/file/40b9f9b025273543a023e.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;借助quickqr的discord机器人生成的猫&#34;
	
	
&gt;
△A cat generated by quickqr&amp;rsquo;s Discord bot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://e7a23aee.dongli.pages.dev/file/dc4a1531b3abc20dc5822.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;同样是quickqr的模型，但融合不够恰当、合理&#34;
	
	
&gt;
△Another model from quickqr, slightly inferior due to inadequate integration&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://e7a23aee.dongli.pages.dev/file/ec1716bae527f3342ca00.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;huggingface的模型，是一座城市的鸟瞰图&#34;
	
	
&gt;
△A bird&amp;rsquo;s-eye view of a city generated by Hugging Face&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://e7a23aee.dongli.pages.dev/file/5b3b4a5e76873269b0d9b.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;huggingface生成的中世纪风格的古堡图片&#34;
	
	
&gt;
△A medieval-style castle image generated by Hugging Face&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;afterword&#34;&gt;Afterword
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article has been written slowly; I started on July 10 and kept writing until the final draft on July 18 (perhaps due to being busy lately). There might be some disjointed sections, and I hope my friends will forgive me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The QR codes generated by qrbtf are among the best AI QR code generation tools I know of. However, it is still in internal testing, and I cannot generate my QR codes with it yet. The codes it generates currently all point to its site. For example, see the image below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://e7a23aee.dongli.pages.dev/file/01edfd6cb8482370c2098.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;图片&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The API key for qrbtf.com in internal testing is qrbtf-ai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, quickqr&amp;rsquo;s bot is also a great tool. The specific operations are not elaborated here; please refer to its official website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Stable Diffusion model on Hugging Face is somewhat less impressive, and the expressions of the generated portraits can be a bit strange.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the URLs:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://qrbtf.com/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://qrbtf.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://quickqr.art/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://quickqr.art/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/spaces/huggingface-projects/QR-code-AI-art-generator&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://huggingface.co/spaces/huggingface-projects/QR-code-AI-art-generator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/spaces/ioclab/ai-qrcode-api&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://huggingface.co/spaces/ioclab/ai-qrcode-api&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/spaces/stabilityai/stable-diffusion&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://huggingface.co/spaces/stabilityai/stable-diffusion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;summary-and-reflection&#34;&gt;Summary and Reflection
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The application of AI in the field of QR codes has brought about tremendous changes in people&amp;rsquo;s lives. It has improved scanning speed and accuracy, expanded the application areas of QR codes, enhanced security mechanisms, and promoted the development of business innovation, leaving people amazed. However, we must also recognize that the application of AI technology is a double-edged sword. The survival of the fittest applies here. Progress in productivity will ultimately leave those who stagnate behind. (As a friend once said.)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>the solution to domain abnormal redirections</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/p/the-solution-of-domain-abnormal-redirections/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://brume.top/en/p/the-solution-of-domain-abnormal-redirections/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, after completing the self-recruitment exam, I completely migrated my original personal website here. It reminded me of when my previous site was hijacked by DNS, so I decided to write a short passage based on what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned, just in case it comes in handy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my old class, during breaks, a group of classmates often gathered around the computer screen to play games. One time, after surfing the internet for a while, they suddenly started shouting excitedly. I looked up to see a few boys running towards me, laughing as they told me my homepage had redirected to another site. By then, they had already closed the redirected site. After checking the browsing history, I was quite surprised. However, when I opened the website that evening at home, it was just as usual. Afterward, analysis revealed that my original site had likely been subjected to DNS hijacking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I had acquired a new domain name, the old site had been abandoned, but the new site still needed protection against DNS hijacking. Below are the methods I use to tackle DNS hijacking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;confirm-whether-your-domain-has-been-subjected-to-dns-hijacking&#34;&gt;Confirm whether your domain has been subjected to DNS hijacking
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A domain that has been hijacked will redirect to other sites regardless of how you access it. In such cases, you can try accessing it via the IP address. If the IP access works fine but the domain keeps redirecting, then your domain has probably been hijacked. In this situation, you need to contact your DNS resolver or server personnel for assistance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;check-if-your-template-files-have-been-altered-with-redirect-codes&#34;&gt;Check if your template files have been altered with redirect codes
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this point, you can temporarily switch to another secure template in the backend. If the redirection stops, it indicates that the redirect code was embedded in the template files.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Redirect codes are often added to JS files, especially the jQuery library, which is frequently targeted. You should check the beginning and end of each JS file for any additional encrypted codes. If you find any, delete them and clear the cache before trying to access the site again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;lntable&#34;&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;1
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;2
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;3
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;4
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;5
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;6
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-HTML&#34; data-lang=&#34;HTML&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;!-- Using meta tag for redirection --&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;meta&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;http-equiv&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;refresh&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;content&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;0;url=http://example.com&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;c&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;!-- Using JavaScript for redirection --&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;script&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;language&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;javascript&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;type&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;text/javascript&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;nb&#34;&gt;window&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;location&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nx&#34;&gt;href&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;http://example.com&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;script&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, you can replace any suspicious files or the entire template package with the original files from the downloaded template zip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;if-switching-templates-still-results-in-redirects-your-cms-or-runtime-environment-might-be-compromised&#34;&gt;If switching templates still results in redirects, your CMS or runtime environment might be compromised
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In such cases, hackers often tamper with the runtime environment, for instance, by hacking Apache or Nginx, automatically injecting redirect codes into web pages. They can even control the frequency, adding code just once a day and only on mobile visits, making it extremely subtle and difficult to trace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this situation, you can resolve the issue by reinstalling the CMS program or uninstalling and reinstalling Apache/Nginx via your server management panel (like &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://bt.cn&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Baota&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;if-problems-persist-your-database-or-server-might-be-hacked&#34;&gt;If problems persist, your database or server might be hacked
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In such cases, it’s best to directly contact the server provider’s staff for assistance, as it’s likely too complex for an ordinary user to resolve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In summary, the overall approach is to identify the specific location of the problem and then address it accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Always remember to back up before making any modifications or fixes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, maintain good security practices for your server and regularly back up your website and database to prevent issues before they arise!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Restart</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/p/restart/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://brume.top/en/p/restart/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The exam to test the results of my three years of learning has ended, and I has spent half my day free. Two months after the database was deleted by mistake and all the blog posts were emptied, I logged into the site again. The intent is clear, I&amp;rsquo;m going to start over.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because I&amp;rsquo;ve been through a lot lately, and when I look at the works I&amp;rsquo;ve written before, I feel that the current me is completely different from the old one. If I compare the text of these two time periods side by side, maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll feel a wonderful contrast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated a lot of things to say, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to spend my pen and ink on the Internet. My mind is still too divergent to write this article titled &amp;ldquo;Restart&amp;rdquo;. I know that I can&amp;rsquo;t slack off, and I am only willing to take advantage of half a day to rebuild the website, which may be regarded as a witness to my own growth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now it seems that &amp;ldquo;restart&amp;rdquo; is the beginning of a new journey; It is the beginning of new dreams and new hopes; It is the beginning of a new growth and a new atmosphere!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a saying that I particularly like - only those who can control time can control their lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am convinced that I will be able to surpass my normal self.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m going to &lt;strong&gt;RESTART&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Hello World</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/p/hello-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://brume.top/en/p/hello-world/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://brume.top&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;春树暮云(Spring trees and evening clouds)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; has been successfully created!
&lt;font color=&#34;red&#34;&gt;&lt;h4&gt;why we call the site &lt;em&gt;Spring trees and evening clouds&lt;/em&gt; ?&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&amp;ldquo;Spring trees and evening clouds&amp;rdquo; is from a piece of poem written by Du Fu, a well-known Chinese poet. In the past, it means missing friends from afar. Now I think it also means pursue our ideals. Spring trees and evining clouds symbolize our unattainable dreams, hard to achieve but also have hope. It&amp;rsquo;s our duty to achieve it, achieve &amp;ldquo;the spring trees and evening clouds&amp;rdquo;。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archives</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/archives/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://brume.top/en/archives/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>About</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/about/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://brume.top/en/about/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About me
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I walk alone in the crimson dusk, feeling like a tiny speck of dust on this melancholy twilight earth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi, there!👋&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Student, AI Player, Front-end Developer, &lt;del&gt;Poet&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Now learning PHP、JavaScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can call me &lt;em&gt;Zephyr Easton&lt;/em&gt; or my Chinese nickname “ 暮云 (mù yún) ”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical Materialist&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The journey has been full of ups and downs, stumbles, and moments of confusion. As a member of the first generation of the 21st century, I now find myself at the forefront of change, witnessing the rise of AIGC technology and the peak of the Web3 industry. Yet, when looking back over time, there are fleeting moments of brilliance that feel solitary, and some hidden joys I long to share with a kindred spirit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After &lt;em&gt;Fan Li&lt;/em&gt;, who now enjoys the peace of yore?&lt;br&gt;Who cares for rain and mist once more, by rivers’ roar?&lt;br&gt;Save for &lt;em&gt;Chao Fu&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Xu You&lt;/em&gt;’s quiet way,&lt;br&gt; none seek today River Ying and Mount Qi’s display.&lt;br&gt;Sigh for the lonely birds at sunset’s door,&lt;br&gt;Laugh at the Peach Blossom Land, whose gates stay no more.&lt;br&gt;Ask immortal &lt;em&gt;Liu&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;br&gt;How many springs have passed?&lt;br&gt;How many blooms shall last?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who are the heroes of the earth, &lt;br&gt;the ones with true worth?&lt;br&gt;He who pours wine by the river&amp;rsquo;s sweep, sword in hand, &lt;em&gt;Cao Cao&lt;/em&gt; stands deep.&lt;br&gt;With banners bright and shields held high, borrowing East Wind’s sigh,&lt;br&gt;Raising &lt;em&gt;Zhuge Liang&lt;/em&gt; from the South, his wisdom so spry,&lt;br&gt;Eightfold arrays would fly.&lt;br&gt;The kingdom’s fate split into three, with one for Shu, and one for Wu, beside the sea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;details&gt;&lt;summary&gt;Original in Chinese&lt;/summary&gt;
鸱夷后那个清闲？谁爱雨笠烟蓑，七里严湍。除却巢由，更无人到，颍水箕山。叹落日孤鸠往还，笑桃源洞口谁关？试问刘郎，几度花开，几度花残？&lt;br&gt;问人间谁是英雄？有酾酒临江，横槊曹公。紫盖黄旗，多应借得，赤壁东风。更惊起南阳卧龙，便成名八阵图中。鼎足三分，一分西蜀，一分江东。
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-the-site&#34;&gt;About the site
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-name&#34;&gt;About the name
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Spring trees and evening clouds (春树暮云)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; was first used as the name of my Chinese blog in 2022. It originates from &lt;em&gt;Du Fu&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo;s poem &lt;em&gt;Spring Day, Recalling Li Bai (《春日忆李白》)&lt;/em&gt;, which expresses how seeing spring trees and evening clouds stirs deep emotions, making one miss distant friends even more, no matter how the seasons change or the sun rises and sets. Back then, I linked it to our pursuit of ideals. The spring trees and evening clouds symbolize the dreams we steadfastly chase—challenging, yet filled with hope. Like spring trees, we hope our dreams flourish with vitality, and like evening clouds, we learn to face life&amp;rsquo;s twilight with calm composure, as in the saying, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Do not lament the setting sun, for its glow still fills the sky. (莫道桑榆晚，为霞尚满天)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I greatly appreciate these two images. The spring trees, of course, are self-explanatory—after all, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;The joy of nurturing growth never ends, one must stay strong and persevere. (春风化雨乐未央，行健不息需自强)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; As for the evening clouds, since middle school, I would often gaze westward after school, to catch the sun&amp;rsquo;s last gentle caress upon the world. In high school, every evening when I returned from the dormitory to the classroom, I would ascend the corridor, eagerly awaiting the sky&amp;rsquo;s embrace of crimson clouds. Such moments are too numerous to recount fully, so I will not list them all here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/f31dcf2d6c8ddc561d5db.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Evening clouds, photographed in Shenzhen,China&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-content-of-the-site&#34;&gt;About the content of the site
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The original intention behind creating my blog was to establish a sanctuary for my soul, a place to sow and nurture thoughts and stories that emerge from the depths of my heart, as well as to share some simple reflections on the reality of the world. I hoped to connect with like-minded friends, yet found myself lost in the complexities of social interactions, unsure of how to touch the chords of shared understanding. What I sought was not the series of value labels assigned by the outside world, nor a deliberately crafted “network of contacts,” but rather a deep friendship grounded purely in shared interests and mutual understanding, something particularly scarce amidst the flow of people in the real world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the cyber realm, I resist the mechanical approach of listing criteria for friendships out of utilitarian motives, knowing that this would only lead the search astray from its original intent, distancing me from sincerity. Thus, I yearn for a pure land—a space where I can breathe freely and express myself without reservation. Here, every word I write is no longer constrained by external judgment; I enjoy a high degree of freedom. I need not worry about whether anyone grows tired of me, nor do I feel compelled to cater to others&amp;rsquo; preferences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the Chinese Internet is flooded with works that have been meticulously optimized for SEO, created purely to attract clicks. Profound insights that could be expressed in just a few words are often cruelly stretched into lengthy articles, where each sentence becomes a carefully laid trap, designed to lure readers into an endless scroll of glaring banner ads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thus, I often ponder that a good online community should not solely pursue monetization, turning into mere content farms; nor should it resemble a train station filled with transient discussions on technology and topics, overwhelmed by a constant influx of strangers. Over time, the ebb and flow of people results in a community that fails to provide a genuine sense of belonging. In the past two or three years, I’ve participated in numerous so-called technical chat groups and online communities, where I earnestly contributed content only to leave without hesitation. In the end, I discovered that writing freely on my own is far more fulfilling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-domian-name-brumetop&#34;&gt;About the domian name brume.top
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;del&gt;不如我(brume) .最厉害(.top)&lt;/del&gt;&lt;br&gt;
brume means clouds&lt;br&gt;
.top is a lovely domain extension&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-history-of-the-site&#34;&gt;About the history of the site
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2021, I wrote several small programs using Visual Basic Script to assist with class management, marking the beginning of my journey into the world of programming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In May 2022, I applied for a free domain and hosting on wordpress.com to start my blog. At that time, the blog name was quite abstract, and I prefer not to reveal it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In December 2022, my application for the free domain eu.org was approved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By the end of December 2022, I migrated my blog to Typecho.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In April 2023, I accidentally deleted the database due to my lack of awareness about cybersecurity and the importance of regular backups, resulting in the loss of a batch of early articles. I managed to recover the first article only through screenshots taken on my phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From 2023 to August 2024, I happily used Typecho to publish articles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On August 20, 2024, I registered the domain brume.top, which provided an opportunity for my blog to update its tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On August 23, 2024, I chose Hugo as the framework for my blog and migrated the blog articles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Links</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/links/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://brume.top/en/links/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Our small site welcomes friend links. Before applying for a friend link, please add our site to your friend links. I will add your link after the review is approved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;details&gt;&lt;summary&gt;Application Guidelines&lt;/summary&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;requirements&#34;&gt;Requirements
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have an independent domain name (the domain suffix must be on the public suffix list).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The entire site must support HTTPS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The site must be created for more than six months (calculated from the publication date of the first blog post).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have more than 10 original articles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The site must not belong to a &amp;ldquo;content farm&amp;rdquo; (see &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.ruanyifeng.com/blog/2024/07/weekly-issue-310.html&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;this article&lt;/a&gt; by Mr. Ruan for details).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should not have excessive advertisements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to exchanging friend links with sites that:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can teach others new knowledge and skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can share personal experiences, broadening others&amp;rsquo; horizons and increasing their knowledge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can be updated regularly, allowing hobbies to continue over the long term.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;apply-for-a-friend-link&#34;&gt;Apply for a Friend Link
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact me via email or apply for a friend link in the comments section below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My email is: hi#brume.top&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please apply for the friend link in Markdown file format, using the following example for your site information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;lntable&#34;&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;1
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;2
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;3
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;4
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; title: 春树暮云(Spring trees and evening clouds)
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  description: 醉困不知醒，欹枕卧江流(Drunk and unaware of waking, lying with cheek on the river&amp;#39;s flow.)
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  website: https://brume.top/
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  image: https://img.brume.top/file/9e5ac94e40fefa5ca5cd4.jpg
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once the application is approved, I will add the friend link. I will try to subscribe to the friend link sites via RSS and will visit the linked sites from time to time. &lt;br&gt;If a friend link site removes our site&amp;rsquo;s link or becomes inaccessible for a long time, I will remove the friend link. &lt;br&gt;If the application is not approved, I will explain the reason, and the webmaster of the unapproved site can choose to remove our site from their friend links.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Search</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/search/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://brume.top/en/search/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
