<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Travels on Spring trees and evening clouds</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/tags/travels/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Travels on Spring trees and evening clouds</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>春树暮云</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://brume.top/en/tags/travels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Glance back to Changsha: like cicadas shed their shell, soaring above the dust.</title>
        <link>https://brume.top/en/p/a-trip-to-changsha/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://brume.top/en/p/a-trip-to-changsha/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://dongli.pages.dev/file/1f6893647f31558236123.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Glance back to Changsha: like cicadas shed their shell, soaring above the dust." /&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By the shore, I wash my feet,&lt;br&gt;
As night’s shadows with currents meet.&lt;br&gt;
In morning light, my short hair dries,&lt;br&gt;
With gentle breezes whispering sighs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Through Wu’s mountains and Chu’s lakes I roam,&lt;br&gt;
Yet long for Xiang, my heart’s true home.&lt;br&gt;
I buy a boat, my cares I leave,&lt;br&gt;
Returning from office, free to believe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Heaven’s favor guides my way,&lt;br&gt;
In June’s warm embrace, I’ll drift and sway,&lt;br&gt;
With fair winds lifting me on the tide,&lt;br&gt;
Floating through waves, I take my stride.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Lofty thoughts, like cicadas shed their shell,&lt;br&gt;
Soaring above the dust.&lt;br&gt;
Like Zhuangzi dreaming of butterfly flight,&lt;br&gt;
I wander where waters and clouds unite.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Faintly I envision—garments of lotus green,&lt;br&gt;
Adorned with autumn orchids, a grace serene,&lt;br&gt;
Attired in elegance, shedding earthly bind.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The goddess of Xiang with a charming smile,&lt;br&gt;
Dances in robes, graceful all the while.&lt;br&gt;
Her delicate fingers pluck strings with care,&lt;br&gt;
Releasing a haunting tune into the air.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Awakening Qu Yuan’s loyal pain,&lt;br&gt;
In &amp;ldquo;Nine Songs&amp;rdquo;, his vows remain.&lt;br&gt;
Words that shine, like sun and moon,&lt;br&gt;
Flow from his sleeve, a timeless tune.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Oh, let not the children know this delight,&lt;br&gt;
The river’s dreams are ours to write.&lt;br&gt;
For this joy in rowing, vast and grand,&lt;br&gt;
Is a treasure meant for our own hand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The upper poem is the translated version of a poem from the Song Dynasty by Zhang Xiaoxiang.It is the work of Zhang Xiaoxiang when he was boating on the Xiangjiang River on the way back to the north. The original poem is shown below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;濯足夜滩急，晞发北风凉。吴山楚泽行遍，只欠到潇湘。买得扁舟归去，此事天公付我，六月下沧浪。蝉蜕尘埃外，蝶梦水云乡。&lt;br&gt;制荷衣，纫兰佩，把琼芳。湘妃起舞一笑，抚瑟奏清商。唤起九歌忠愤，拂拭三闾文字，还与日争光。莫遣儿辈觉，此乐未渠央。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, our school organized a study trip to Hunan, spanning five days. During this time, we traveled between Changsha and Shaoshan, exploring both rural and urban landscapes, witnessing the fusion and collision of traditional culture and modern society, strolling by the lakes and rivers, and contemplating the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;day-1-setting-off&#34;&gt;Day 1: Setting Off!
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Midday, the entire grade, teachers, and staff gathered at Shenzhen North Railway Station, to board the high-speed train bound for Changsha. Arriving at noon, the weather was surprisingly mild, a rare treat in the South.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/df5adcca9f980df039859.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;深圳北站远景&#34;
	
	
&gt;
△A faraway look of Shenzhen North Railway Station&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After an hour’s wait, we finally boarded the sleek Fuxing Electric Multiple Unit. Its modern design and technology showcased our school’s commitment to student comfort and efficiency. Riding the high-speed rail instead of the slower options not only enhanced our travel experience, but also reflected our nation’s advancements in transportation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/e41e2239142abfb175247.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;高铁车头&#34;
	
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/618e199679baf4e3e05c6.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;复兴号&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before boarding, I snapped a few photos of the train as I walked along.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scenery outside the window, from the alluvial plains of the Pearl River Delta to the karst landscapes of northern Guangdong, and the hills and plains of both southern and northern Hunan, was all breathtaking!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approaching Guangzhou, rain began to fall, adding a touch of Jiangnan charm to our journey as we glimpsed barges on distant rivers under misty skies.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/25d27fa4a35b5c16896d5.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;一条河，应该是珠江的支流&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then we made stops at Shaoguan, Chenzhou, and Hengyang before arriving at Changsha South Station, a journey of approximately three and a half hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/090ef6ec71df637ea0906.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;长沙南站附近的公路&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From there, we boarded a bus near Changsha South Station. I was fortunate to sit in the front row, offering one of the best views. After a meal and a nighttime cruise on the Liuyang River, we stayed overnight at a hotel near Huanghua Airport, concluding our first day’s journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;day-2-blending-old-with-new&#34;&gt;Day 2: Blending Old with New
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Returning to downtown Changsha, we began the day with a visit to the Hunan Provincial Museum, renowned for its artifacts excavated from the Han Dynasty tombs at Mawangdui. On the third floor, we watched a captivating light show played every half hour on the tomb’s sidewalls. Shadows danced on walls over ten meters deep, bringing to life ancient clothing and auspicious patterns, evoking a sense of reverence and mystery akin to a religious experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/650e1f5638bdcd4491cd8.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;灯光演出，看台上挤满了人&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The picture below is a picture of the grave pit before the performance. You can refer to the people in the stands and estimate the depth of the triangle with the relevant knowledge of the triangle that you learned in junior high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/c2b72f84962b60c214622.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;墓坑&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, we crossed the Xiang River to visit Hunan University, Yuelu Academy, and Aiwan Pavilion. Known as a &amp;ldquo;millennium-old academy,&amp;rdquo; Hunan University exudes a strong academic atmosphere amidst serene surroundings. At the entrance, university students dressed in traditional attire added youthful vigor to the campus.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/dcb3f561ce97af139d5c7.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;湖南大学的一栋建筑&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, we explored Yuelu Academy. Towering ancient trees and flowing waters adorned the site, where every stone inscription and historic building reflected the deep cultural heritage of Hunan. Amidst these ancient halls, we connected with the wisdom of past scholars, experiencing firsthand the cultural richness encapsulated in the phrase, &amp;ldquo;Only Chu produces talent, and here it reaches its peak(惟楚有材，于斯为盛)&amp;rdquo;.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/dab50c233fc26466d37d7.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;惟楚有材，于斯为盛&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continuing north from the academy towards Aiwan Pavilion, we encountered Tang Bohu’s poetic sentiment. Despite it is now the modern era, it was difficult not to imagine Tang Bohu’s leisurely mood at that time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I paint the azure Yangtze’s flow,&lt;br&gt;Maple leaves at Aiwan Pavilion woe.&lt;br&gt;Autumn moon gently bathes the Buddhist shrine,&lt;br&gt;Incense smoke curls around the scripture hall divine.&lt;br&gt;(我画蓝江水悠悠，爱晚亭上枫叶愁。秋月溶溶照佛寺，香烟袅袅绕经楼。)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/499cea4a396e002b78089.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;爱晚亭&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We then returned along the same route to visit Taiping Old Street for field research (actually, it was shopping). Despite being touted as &amp;ldquo;the street with the most intact original street pattern of ancient Changsha,&amp;rdquo; it unfortunately fell short of preserving its cultural essence, appearing somewhat homogeneous and commercialized. Adjacent sites, such as Jia Yi’s former residence, seemed out of place.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/dc6b915c65fc9d3cf50ab.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;太平老街&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, Taiping Old Street’s &amp;ldquo;Black Classic&amp;rdquo; stinky tofu was indeed delicious and reasonably priced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During free time on Taiping Old Street, I experienced Changsha’s metro system. The stations resembled those in Shenzhen, but amenities inside the Shenzhen metro trains, such as display screens, announcements, and station cleanliness, surpassed those in Changsha’s metro.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/739ad4a3931b28f7658d3.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;长沙地铁&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;day-3-embracing-tradition&#34;&gt;Day 3: Embracing Tradition
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;From Changsha to Shaoshan, our journey took about three hours, arriving at the research and practice base in Huangtian Village, where we met local farmers and engaged in activities such as fishing in rice fields and transplanting seedlings, followed by a meal at a farmhouse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huangtian Village’s picturesque surroundings included roadside encounters with some unnamed wildflowers.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/2f0463b6f5d91446dd0da.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;黄田村野花&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, we visited the Mao Zedong Memorial Museum in Shaoshan, learning about Chairman Mao’s leadership in completing China’s historical tasks against imperialism and feudalism, establishing the People’s Republic of China, and advancing socialism’s glorious history. Afterwards, we visited the great man’s former residence. The environment was excellent, with a half-acre lotus pond in front of the house, giving it a feeling of &amp;ldquo;repeating lakes and overlapping peaks, clear and splendid&amp;rdquo;.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/30b5d6cc284310b6dfd78.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;毛主席故居&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nearby, I unexpectedly met two middle school classmates who were also participating in the study tour, now attending another high school. We discussed our studies and lives over the past year and the new changes in our lives as we entered a new stage. Finally, we took a group photo and parted ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After dinner, we watched the large-scale live performance &amp;ldquo;China Gave Birth to Mao Zedong&amp;rdquo; in Shaoshan. We watched from a high platform, enjoying the spacious venue. Opening my map app on my phone, I surprisingly found a satellite image that clearly resembled a map of China. (Taiwan Province and Hainan Province are on the bottom right of the theater.)
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/03170402df8a6ce2a87ff-c0a7d1b2bffe126517.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;satellite image&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scene at the event was as shown in the following image. The dazzling lights of the performance were truly awe-inspiring.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/ea560c7437020a4044373.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;演出&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We stayed overnight at a hotel in the Huitang town near Changsha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;day-4-inspiring-our-nation&#34;&gt;Day 4: Inspiring Our Nation
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Returning to Changsha after more than two hours by bus, we visited the First Normal School in the morning, Chairman Mao’s alma mater. In the afternoon, we visited Orange Island.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Orange Island sits atop the Xiang River, with a narrow and elongated shape. We took a small train from the north of Orange Island, heading south to the tip of Orange Island. The school planned for the entire grade to take a large group photo on the square at the tip of Orange Island. We arrived early and had spare time to stroll along the shore with classmates. The slow flow of the Xiang River and its wide surface offered a pleasant view of the water flowing south and many boats passing by.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/4f0650ecaaac5f79a4124.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;湘江&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Song Dynasty poet Zhang Xiaoxiang praised:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;濯足夜滩急，晞发北风凉。吴山楚泽行遍，只欠到潇湘。买得扁舟归去，此事天公付我，六月下沧浪。蝉蜕尘埃外，蝶梦水云乡。&lt;br&gt;制荷衣，纫兰佩，把琼芳。湘妃起舞一笑，抚瑟奏清商。唤起九歌忠愤，拂拭三闾文字，还与日争光。莫遣儿辈觉，此乐未渠央。(English translation is shown on the top of the page)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really like the meaning in this lyric, a blend of Su Shi’s broad-mindedness and Li Qingzhao’s fresh and elegant style, between a clear and high-minded mood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After taking the group photo, we went to the Mao Zedong Youth Art Statue north of Orange Isle. The sculpture’s eyes were bright, just like Chairman Mao’s &amp;ldquo;We criticized with all our might, pointing to stream and hill, writing in blame or praise (指点江山，激扬文字)&amp;rdquo; demeanor.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/126a152ca347a34270d31.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;雕像&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later in the evening, we returned near Shaoshan and held a bonfire party. The fireworks at the bonfire party were exciting, breaking the silence of the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align =&#34;center&#34;&gt;&lt;video src=&#34;https://video.gumlet.io/65b99c6ae5f634aafa2ef6a0/668a43c4517fbad3e8038e27/download.mp4&#34; controls=&#34;controls&#34; width=&#34;80%&#34; &gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I can’t sing, I didn’t sign up for the class chorus performance. However, during our class performance, a few of my good friends lifted me onto the stage. This scene was seen by my classmates who work at the TV station, who filmed it as a &amp;ldquo;highlight&amp;rdquo; of the event and aired it on the TV program. Now I’m somewhat famous throughout the school~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;day-5returning-home&#34;&gt;Day 5：Returning Home
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the morning, we visited the Yuan Longping Rice Museum, and in the afternoon, we took the high-speed train back to Shenzhen by evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/fc26ba5b1b84c626256d4.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;速度&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the return train made fewer stops, we arrived at the Shenzhen North Railway Station in three hours. We dispersed near it, concluding our study tour successfully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this study tour, we learned about culture, history, and heritage. Today, in the midst of prosperity and standing in the grand tide of the &amp;ldquo;great changes unseen in a century&amp;rdquo;, we are fortunate to have an unprecedented broad vision, to stand at the pinnacle of history, and to look forward to the distant and brilliant future. The magnificent picture of national rejuvenation slowly unfolds before our eyes, inspiring and urging us forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Therefore, as the gatherers of new knowledge, explorers of new thoughts, and the surfers of the new era, we naturally shoulder a heavy and sacred mission. &amp;ldquo;So many deeds cry out to be done, and always urgently; the world rolls on, time presses. (多少事，从来急，天地转，光阴迫)&amp;rdquo; As the future of the nation and the hope of the nation, we deeply understand the weight of responsibility and the honor of the mission. We pledge to use China’s unique wisdom, innovative solutions, and firm actions to outline and shape a better world tomorrow, allowing China’s voice to resonate globally and making the world more splendid because of our young generation!
&lt;img src=&#34;https://dongli.pages.dev/file/1515c655213246bca8129.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;#&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
